Guide to the Reynolds Price Papers, 1880-2014 RL.01050
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1946-2014, undated
  The (2) Writings Series contains various writings by Price and is divided into the Books, Scribner's Files, Uncollected Fiction and Nonfiction, Price Writing in Serials, Reviews by Price, Addresses and Speeches, and Audiovisual Recordings of Price Regarding Writing subseries. The Books subseries is composed chiefly of drafts, typescripts, and proofs of Price's novels, plays, autobiographical works, and volumes of poetry, many with Price's notations and revisions, and provides a thorough representation of the development of each. Following his death, DUL received the materials for the books Letter to a Godchild; Ardent Spirits; and, Midstream, which were added to their own sub-subseries. Scribner, Price's longtime publisher, provided the materials in Scribner's Files, offering insight into the publishing process. Materials include correspondence, proposals, editing and production notes, marketing and promotion information, and reviews. The Price Writing in Serials subseries contains published essays, poems, and short stories. The Reviews by Price subseries includes Price's writing about other artists' work. Transcripts of his speeches and interviews appear in the Speeches and Addresses subseries. And the Audiovisual Recordings of Price Regarding Writing subseries includes recordings of Price discussing, reading, or performing his written materials and is arranged chronologically.
  - Books, long works, 1957-2012, undated
    The majority of Price's published books and plays (minus some small press publications and limited editions) appear in order of publication date. For each book, materials are then arranged in order of their writing and editing history. In cases of approximate or inferred dates, strict chronological order is occasionally ignored, with the main sequence of writing and editing the text--as reflected in notes, manuscripts, typescripts, and proofs--being favored over such later matters in the publication process as jacket copy, ads, and adaptations into other genres and media (such as screenplays and audiobooks).
    - Long and Happy Life, 1957-2008, undated; 73 folders
      - Notes and drafts, 1957-1961; 18 folders (Box 69)
      - John Vermeer painting that inspired A Long and Happy Life, undated (Box 354)
      - Notes and drafts, 1961, undated; 9 folders (Box 70)
        Includes notes, drafts, handwritten manuscript, fair copy, and typescripts.
      - Proofs, corrected pages, 1961 (Box 70)
      - Screenplay, draft by Charles Eastman, 1961; 2 folders (Box 70)
      - Screenplay, notes and drafts, 1965-1989; 17 folders (Box 71)
        Includes fair copies, drafts by, and for Jack Garfein, Richard Neubert, John Clum for Duke Summer Theater, Stephanie Keys, and Beth Henley. Price's revisions are included on some draft copies.
      - A Long and Happy Life, final dress rehearsal, Duke Summer Theatre, 1976 July 8 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0096)
      - Proofs, undated; 4 folders (Box 71)
        Includes a dedication page, Encounter proof of Part One, jacket sketch by Harry Ford, and photocopies of the paperback cover.
      - Screenplay, drafts, 1990-1991, undated; 5 folders (Box 72)
      - Notes and drafts, 2008 Nov-Dec; 4 folders (Box 305)
        Includes drafts and paperback design.
      - Proof, 2008 Dec (Box 72)
      - Notes and drafts, undated (Box 72)
      - Notes and drafts, electronic documents, 1991, undated; 5 items 5 MS Word files; 280 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Drafts of Long and Happy Life screenplay, and related correspondence.
      - Electronic correspondence, 1991 Aug 6 (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Letter to Bruce and Nan.
      - Reviews, 1987, undated (Box 73)
        Includes review of Reynolds Price: The Spring in the Depth of the Forest, translation of Long and Happy Life by Gudrun Bergmann.
      - Proofs, 1961-1964; 3 folders (Box 82)
      - Notes and drafts, undated (Box 82)
      - A Long and Happy Life serialization, 1963 Feb 16 -Mar 23; 6 folders (Box 166)
        In German, by Margaret Sander.
    - The Names and Faces of Heroes, 1951-1963, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1951-1963, undated; 19 folders (Box 74)
        Includes notes and drafts for stories included in the volume, including A Chain of Love; Michael Egerton; The Warrior Princess Ozimba; The Anniversary; and Uncle Grant. Materials include manuscripts and revised typescripts.
      - Notes and drafts, 1963; 2 folders (Box 74)
        Includes printer's transcript.
      - Proofs, 1963, undated; 4 folders (Box 74)
        Includes jacket, plate, and sample proofs.
      - Proofs, 1963, undated; 3 folders (Box 82)
        Includes jacket proof.
      - Reviews, 1963 Aug (Box 74)
    - A Generous Man, 1964-1966, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1964-1965, undated; 12 folders (Box 75)
        Includes first draft manuscripts, and revised typescripts.
      - Notes and drafts, 1966, undated; 6 folders (Box 76)
      - Synopsis for Columbia Pictures Corporation, 1966 Feb (Box 76)
        Includes plate proofs, proof in French, and jacket proofs.
      - Proofs, 1966, 1970, undated; 7 folders (Box 76)
      - Proofs, 1966; 4 folders (Box 82)
      - Reviews and publicity, 1966 May 2 (Box 76)
      - Reviews and publicity, 1966 (Oversize-folder 2)
        Includes advertisement placed in New York Times.
    - Love and Work, 1965-1968, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1965-1968, undated; 6 folders (Box 76)
        Includes first draft manuscripts and revised typescripts.
      - Notes and drafts, 1968; 5 folders (Box 77)
        Includes draft of jacket copy.
      - Proofs, 1968, undated; 3 folders (Box 77)
        Includes plate and jacket proofs.
      - Proofs, 1968; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - Permanent Errors, 1963-1982, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1963-1970, undated; 15 folders (Box 77)
        Includes notes and drafts for stories included in the volume, including To the Reader, The Happiness of Others, A Dog's Death, Scars, Waiting at Dachau, Late Warnings, Invitation for Jesse Rehder, Summer Games, Truth and Lies, Good and Bad Dreams, and, Walking Lessons.
      - Notes and drafts, 1970, undated; 14 folders (Box 78)
        Includes annotations by Price and Henry Ford.
      - Proofs, 1970; 4 folders (Box 78)
      - Proofs, 1970, undated; 3 folders (Box 79)
        Includes page proof boxed by Stuart Wright, jacket proofs, and paperback cover.
      - Notes and drafts, 1970-1982, undated; 2 folders (Box 79)
        Includes jacket copy.
      - Proofs, 1970; 4 folders (Box 84)
    - Things Themselves, 1963-1972, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1963-1972, undated; 13 folders (Box 79)
        Includes notes and drafts for stories included in the volume, including To The Reader; Dodging Apples; Five Sketches for a Screenplay; News for the Mineshaft; Pylon - The Posture of Worship; A Reasonable Guide Through Perilous Seas; The Onlooker, Smiling; Frightening Gift; The Wings of a Dove - A Single Combat; Dodo, Phoenix, or Tough Old Cock?; and, For Ernest Hemingway.
      - Notes and drafts, 1971-1972, undated; 6 folders (Box 80)
        Includes notes and drafts for stories included in the volume, including For Ernest Hemingway; Four Abrahams, Four Isaacs by Rembrandt; and, Poem Doctrinal and Exemplary to a Nation.
      - Proofs, 1972; 4 folders (Box 80)
      - Proofs, 1972; 4 folders (Box 84)
    - Presence and Absence, 1972-1973
      - Notes and drafts, 1972; 3 folders (Box 80)
      - Proofs, 1972-1973 (Box 80)
      - Proofs, 1973 (Box 84)
        Includes Price's corrections.
    - The Surface of Earth, 1972-1995, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1972-1973, undated; 2 folders (Box 80)
        Includes first draft manuscript.
      - Notes and drafts, 1972-1974, undated; 11 folders (Box 81)
      - Notes and drafts, 1975, undated; 9 folders (Box 83)
      - Notes and drafts, undated (Box 275)
        Includes character and location notes.
      - Proofs, 1976, 1981-1983, undated; 5 folders (Box 83)
        Includes cover photographs, and corrections from Price.
      - Proofs, 1973, 1975; 4 folders (Box 84)
      - Proofs, 1975; 4 folders (Box 86)
      - Reviews, 1975 (Box 80)
    - Early Dark, 1976-1978, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1976-1977; 6 folders (Box 85)
      - Proofs, sample pages, 1976 Jul-Aug (Box 85)
      - Proofs, 1977; 3 folders (Box 86)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 320)
      - Photographs, 1978 May 6 (Box 354)
        Unidentified cast member, signed by cast.
      - Early Dark - WPA Theatre, 1978 April 12, May 6; 3 items (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0098 - RL01050-CS-0100)
      - Music for Early Dark Ross Levy (WPA Theatre), 1978 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0101)
    - A Palpable God, 1975-1979, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1975-1978, undated; 12 folders (Box 85)
      - Proofs, 1976 (Box 85)
        Includes proof with corrections.
      - Proofs, 1977-1978; 5 folders (Box 88)
        Includes proofs with Price's corrections.
      - Notes and drafts, 1978-1979, undated; 6 folders (Box 87)
    - Lessons Learned, proofs, At the Gulf, 1977 (Box 86)
    - Nine Mysteries, 1977, 1979, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1977, 1979, undated; 9 folders (Box 87)
        Includes notes and drafts for poems including Annunciation; Ascension; Dead Girl; Naked Boy; Reparation; and, Resurrection.
      - Proofs, 1977, undated; 4 folders (Box 87)
        Includes printing proofs and cover.
    - Source of Light, 1971-1995, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1971-1980; 8 folders (Box 87)
        Includes notes, fragments, manuscripts, and typescripts.
      - Notes and drafts, 1980-1981, 1995, undated; 12 folders (Box 89)
      - Proofs, undated; 2 folders (Box 89)
        Includes binding proof, and paperback cover.
      - Proof, plate, 1981 (Box 90)
      - Proofs, 1981; 4 folders (Box 88)
      - Publicity, 1982 (Oversize-folder 2)
        Advertising for reading at Reynolda House.
    - Vital Provisions, 1961-1963, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1961-1983, undated; 34 folders (Box 89)
        Includes notes and drafts for poems including The Alchemist; Angel; Anniversary; The Annual Heron; Annunciation; At the Gulf; Attis; Aurora; Black Water; Christ Child's Song at the End of Night; Cumaean Song; Dead Girl; Divine Propositions; The Dream of a House; The Dream of Food; The Dream of Lee; For Leontyne Price After Ariadne; Found, For My Brother; I Say of Any Man; Instruction (Matthew (27:5); Man and Faun; Memoranda; Night Speech; Pictures of the Dead; Pure Boys and Girls; Questions for a Student (A.M. 18 Mar 1969); A Rainbow and a Day-Old Calf; Seafarer; Sleeping Wife (Matthew 27:19); Ten Years, Four Days; To My Niece--Our Photograph in a Hammock; Torso of an Archaic Apollo; and, Your Element.
      - Proofs, At the Gulf, 1977 (Box 86)
      - Notes and drafts, 1981-1982, undated; 7 folders (Box 91)
        Includes author's questionnaire, revised fair copy, and typescripts.
      - Proofs, 1982; 4 folders (Box 91)
    - Mustian, 1982-1984, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1982 Nov (Box 91)
      - Proofs, with Price's corrections, 1983 (Box 91)
      - Proofs, 1983-1984, undated; 3 folders (Box 92)
        Includes Price's corrections, advertisements, and covers.
      - Notes and drafts, undated (Box 92)
    - Private Contentment, 1976-1984, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1981, 1984; 4 folders (Box 92)
      - Shooting script for PBS American Playhouse, 1982; 2 folders (Box 92)
      - Proofs, 1984 (Box 92)
      - Proofs, 1984 (Box 88)
      - Reviews, 1984 (Box 92)
      - Stage plan, 1985 (Oversize-folder 2)
      - Cover photographs, 1976, undated (Box 320)
        Includes photographs for The Laws of Ice; Private Contentment; and, The Surface of the Earth.
    - Kate Vaiden, 1983-2000, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1983-1985; 4 folders (Box 92)
        Includes manuscripts and typescripts.
      - Notes and drafts, 1985-1986, undated; 10 folders (Box 93)
      - Proofs, 1986 (Box 93)
      - Proofs, master, 1986; 4 folders (Box 94)
        Includes Price's corrections, jacket sketch, and sketch.
      - Proofs, cover, undated (Box 90)
      - Screenplay by Benedict Fitzgerald, 1987; 3 folders (Box 95)
      - Reviews, 2000 Aug 27 (Box 95)
    - The Laws of Ice, 1966-1986, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1966-1968, 1978-1984, undated; 29 folders (Box 95)
        Includes revised notes and drafts for poems including The Aim; Ambrosia; Before the Flood; Caught; Caw; Cherokee; The Claim; Dead Man, Dying Girl; Eels; Epitaphs from the Greek Anthology; For James Dean; For Vivien Leigh; Good Places; Hawk Hill; The Heaven of Elizabeth Rodwell, My Mother; His Discovery; House Snake; I Am Transmuting; Jonathan's Lament for David; Last Conversation; A Life in Dreams; Lighthouse, Mosquito Inlet; The Lines of Life; Midnight; Pears; and, Porta Nigra.
      - Proofs, 1966, 1996; 2 folders (Box 95)
        Includes proof of The Lines of Life and The Sleeper in the Valley, from Shenandoah
      - Notes and drafts, 1960-1966, 1982-1986, undated; 16 folders (Box 96)
        Includes revised notes and drafts for poems including Rest; Rincon 1; Rincon 2; Same Road; Secret; The Sleeper in the Valley; Three Visits; A Tomb for Will Price, My Father; Transatlantic; Vision; Warm Springs; Watchman, Tower, Midnight; and, What is Godly.
    - A Common Room, 1964-1987, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1966-1967, 1973-1978, 1981-1982, undated; 19 folders (Box 96)
        Includes notes and revised drafts for poems including The Aim; Ambrosia; Before the Flood; Caught; Caw; Cherokee; The Claim; Dead Man, Dying Girl; Eels; Epitaphs from the Greek Anthology; For James Dean; For Vivien Leigh; Good Places; Hawk Hill; The Heaven of Elizabeth Rodwell, My Mother; His Discovery; House Snake; I Am Transmuting; Jonathan's Lament for David; Last Conversation; A Life in Dreams; Lighthouse, Mosquito Inlet; The Lines of Life; Midnight; Pears; and, Porta Nigra.
      - Proofs, 1986, undated (Box 96)
      - Proofs, 1976, 1987; 3 folders (Box 97)
        Includes Harry Ford's and Price's corrections, and You Are Needed Now and Always Will Be.
      - Proofs, 1975 (Oversize-folder 3)
        This oversize folders includes You Are Needed Now and Always Will Be, galleys for Esquire magazine.
      - Notes and drafts, 1964-1982, 1986-1987, undated; 19 folders (Box 98)
        Includes notes and revised drafts of essays including The Thing Itself; Uses for Freedoms; A Vast Common Room; What Stayed in the Plains; and, You Are Needed Now and Will Always Be.
      - Proofs, undated; 2 folders (Box 99)
        Includes jacket sketch by Harry Ford, and jacket.
    - Full Moon, 1987-1993, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1987-1988; 7 folders (Box 99)
        Includes typescripts with Price's corrections, and bound copy.
      - Proofs, corrected, 1993; 2 folders (Box 99)
      - Reviews, 1993 Apr (Box 99)
      - Full Moon, undated; 3 folders (Box 320)
    - Good Hearts, 1986-1988, undated
      - Typescript draft, 1986, 1988, undated; 6 folders (Box 100)
        Includes ad copy, and publicity schedule.
      - Proofs, 1988; 4 folders (Box 100)
        Includes Price's and Harry Ford's corrections.
      - Good Hearts, 1988 Aug 4 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0106)
    - Clear Pictures, 1987-2008, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1987-1988, 2006, undated; 4 folders (Box 100)
      - Proofs, 1989; 3 folders (Box 94)
        Includes notes on illustrations.
      - Notes and drafts, 1987, undated; 16 folders (Box 101)
        Includes notes and revised drafts of essays, and binding die copy, including Black Help; An Absolute Hunter; A Normal, All But Fatal Childhood; Real Copies; Credible Light, (Absolute Reality); A Final Secret: Will's Death; Afterword (Epilogue); captions for illustrations; A Note on Clear Pictures; Forward; Three Useful Lessons; and, An Open Heart.
      - Notes and drafts, 1989; 3 folders (Box 102)
      - Notes and drafts, 2008 Dec (Box 305)
      - Proofs, 1989, undated; 4 folders (Box 102)
        Includes corrected proof, jacket, and promotional folder.
      - Book cover, 1989 (Box 73)
      - Reviews, 1989 (Box 73)
      - Reviews, 1994-1995 (Box 102)
      - Reviews, 2009 Jan (Box 305)
      - Documentary Reviews, 1994 Mar 10-1995 Jun 28, undated (Box 102)
      - Photographs, 1988, undated; 3 folders (Box 320)
        Includes reproductions.
      - Film, photographs, 1998, undated; 2 folders (Box 320)
      - Publicity, 1994 (Box 354)
        Includes a poster for the documentary.
      - Side A: Storylines Southeast #12; Side B: Clear Pictures, undated (Box 292, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0044)
      - Storylines Southeast #12, 1999 Dec 19 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0020)
      - Storylines Southeast #12, undated (Box 291, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0024)
    - The Tongues of Angels, 1987-1991, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1987, undated; 7 folders (Box 102)
        Includes research notes, and revised typescripts.
      - Proof, 1989 (Box 102)
      - Notes and drafts, 1989, undated; 5 folders (Box 103)
        Includes revised typescripts, and, Ultramarine Publishing Company flyer.
      - Reviews, 1990 (Box 103)
      - Proofs, undated (Box 94)
        Includes sample covers.
      - Screenplay, 1991 Aug-Sep (Box 103)
      - Notes and drafts, electronic documents, undated; 11 items 11 MS Word files; 500 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes screenplay drafts; lists of character names; and, a letter to Bruce and Nan.
    - The Use of Fire, 1960-1990, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1960-1977, 1986-1990, undated; 34 folders (Box 103)
      - Proof, printer's, 1990 Jul (Box 103)
      - Proof, printer's, 1990 (Box 94)
      - Proofs, book cover, 1990 (Box 73)
    - New Music: A Trilogy, 1984-2006, undated
      - Notes and drafts, reviews, August Snow, 1984-1985, 2006; 8 folders (Box 104)
        Includes notes and revised manuscript and typescript drafts of the play August Snow. Also includes rehearsal notes, and the Hendrix Players production program.
      - Notes and drafts, New Music, 1985; 6 folders (Box 104)
        Includes notes and revised manuscript and typescript drafts the play August Snow. Includes manuscript and typescript drafts, rehearsal notes, and the Hendrix Players production program.
      - Notes and drafts, Better Days, 1985; 3 folders (Box 104)
      - Notes and drafts: New Music, A Trilogy, 1987, 1989-1990; 9 folders (Box 105)
      - Better Days Tape 1, 1986 Dec 5 (Box 290, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0104)
      - Better Days Tape 2, 1986 Dec 5 (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0105)
      - Better Days - Act I, Act II, undated; 2 items (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0115 - RL01050-CS-0116)
      - New Music - Act I, Act II, undated; 2 items (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0117 - RL01050-CS-0118)
      - August Snow, undated (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0121)
      - Articles and Reviews, August Snow and Night Dance, 1998 Dec 16-2000 Dec 5 (Box 104)
      - Publicity, 1991 (Box 168)
        Includes a photographs of the Night Dance cast.
      - Electronic correspondence, 1992 Oct 11 (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes correspondence to Terry Nemeth regarding book jacket.
    - The Foreseeable Future, 1988-1991, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1988, undated; 3 folders (Box 105)
        Includes early drafts of The Fare to The Moon.
      - Notes and drafts, 1988 (Box 106)
      - Proofs, 1990-1991; 5 folders (Box 106)
        Includes setting copy with Price's revisions, page proof, and jacket illustration.
      - Notes and drafts, electronic correspondence, 1990; 1 Files 1 MS Word doc; 4 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes correspondence with Lee Goerner regarding jacket.
      - Reviews, 1991 (Box 73)
    - Blue Calhoun, 1985-2001, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1990; 2 folders (Box 106)
      - Notes and drafts, 1991, undated; 9 folders (Box 107)
      - Notes and drafts, 1991, undated; 8 folders (Box 108)
      - Notes and drafts, 1991; 4 folders (Box 109)
        Includes printer's typescript, and revised fragments.
      - Notes and drafts, electronic documents, undated; 16 items 16 MS Word files; 307 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes drafts and correspondence regarding issuing complimentary copies of Blue Calhoun.
      - Proofs, 1992; 7 folders (Box 109)
        Includes publisher's prospectus.
      - Proofs, 1991; 2 folders (Box 94)
        Includes proofreader's and master galleys.
      - Proofs, undated (Box 110)
      - Notes, undated (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes a note to publisher with list of complimentary copies from author.
      - Notes and drafts, 1986 Jun 9 (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes a draft of letter from Grandfather.
      - Notes and drafts, 1985 Jun 8 (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes a draft letter.
      - Notes and drafts, 2001 (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes a draft of 57 pages.
      - Notes and drafts, 2001 (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes a draft of an unformatted title page.
      - Reviews and publicity, 1992 Apr 6-Oct 16, undated; 9 folders (Box 109)
    - The Collected Stories, 1988-2004, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1988-1992, 1997, undated; 22 folders (Box 111)
        Includes drafts and typescripts for stories including The Company of the Dead; Deeds of Light; An Early Christmas; The Enormous Door; The Final News; The Golden Child; A Final Account; His Final Mother; Home; Long Night; A New Piece of Woods; Slow Night; This Wait; Watching Her Die; and, typescripts of the complete draft.
      - Notes and drafts, 1991-1992; 4 folders (Box 225)
      - Notes and drafts, 1992, 2004; 8 folders (Box 112)
      - Notes and drafts, front matter and jacket copy, 1992, 2003, undated (Box 113)
      - Notes and drafts, 1996-2000, undated; 36 Files 36 MS Word files and email documents; 658 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes drafts of A Final Account; A New Stretch of Woods; An Evening Meal; A Told Secret; Bess Waters; Breath; The Company of the Dead; Early Christmas; Breath; Deeds of Light; Endless Mountains; Full Day; Good Night; His Final Mother; The Last of a Long Correspondence; The Last News; Long Night; Near Day; Night and Silence; Nine Hours Alone; Serious Need; This Wait; Toward Home; and, Two Useful Visits. Drafts of the forward, and the table of contents are also included.
      - Proofs, 1992; 2 folders (Box 112)
      - Proofs, 1992-1993, undated; 9 folders (Box 113)
        Includes corrected page proofs.
      - Proofs, 1993 Jan 19-20; 4 folders (Box 110)
      - Reviews and publicity, 1993 Feb 28-1994 Jul 17, undated (Box 113)
    - A Whole New Life, 1992-2003, undated
      - Notes and drafts, 1992-1993; 10 folders (Box 114)
        Includes typescript drafts with Price's revisions.
      - Notes and drafts, 1993 Apr-Jul; 10 folders (Box 115)
        Includes typescript drafts with Price's revisions, and notes and correspondence from Daniel Voll, and Alec Wilkinson.
      - Notes and drafts, 1993-1994, 2003, undated; 6 folders (Box 116)
        Includes drafts of jacket copy, and front cover.
      - Proofs, 1993-1994, 1999-2000; 5 folders (Box 116)
      - Proofs, jacket, undated (Box 110)
      - Proofs, cover, 1994 (Box 349)
      - A Whole New Life, undated (Box 300, Audio-cassette RL01050-CS-0119)
      - Reviews and publicity, 1994 Mar 1-2001 Jan 7, undated; 2 folders (Box 116)
      - Notes and drafts, electronic documents, undated; 13 Files 13 MS Word docs; 844 KB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
        Includes undated drafts.